they came to your land, they slaughtered your
они пришли на вашу землю вырезали ваших
people, they captured
людей захватили
everything, well, there are things to say, there are
всё ну бывают что сказать
Hello, hello, hello
Здравствуйте здравствуйте здравствуйте
from the city of Khmelnitsky Where are you from?
из города Хмельницкий Вы откуда откуда
From Moscow Cool Wow Do you have an entire
Из Москвы
wall
Прикольно Ничего себе У тебя вся стена
made of a flag or
из флага что ли состоит что нет пойму
something?  in
отдельно Ничего себе она Прям вся в
Ukraine, damn I got it And where are you from
Украине блин Понял А ты откуда сам
wait for the city
подожди город город
what city is Khmelnitsky yes And where are you from
какой Хмельницкий да А ты откуда
in Chechnya in Chechnya I understood and
сам в Чечни в Чечни понял а флаг у
your flag is a Palestinian flag Well, I see Yes
тебя флаг палестинский Ну а я же вижу Да
and not
а не
Chechnya chnya I only have it in
Чечни чня У меня есть только она на
another place I got it But
другом месте понял А вот
look, it’s interesting, I remember when I
смотри токо интересно вот я помню когда
was little in the nineties, Russia
был маленький девяностые года Россия
killed Chechens Yes, there are 300,000 Chechens there,
убивала чеченцев Да там 300.000 чеченцев
not only I was interested in this
у не не просто мне интересно было такое
or
или не
not, Well, there was a war Yes, I understand, that is,
было Ну война была Да понял то есть
Russia bombed
Россия бомба бомбардировать
Grozny How many children died
Грозный Сколько сколько детей погибло
because of Russia
из-за России
[music  ]
[музыка]
officially
официально
40,000 is a lot, very 40,000 children Yes, I
40.000 это много очень 40.000 детей Да
understand, but in Gaza How many children
понял а в газе Сколько сейчас детей
have died now?
погибло
17,000 So it turns out that in Grozny, in
17.000 се То есть получается в Грозном в
Grozny alone, more children died than in
одном Грозном погибло детей больше чем в
ha, not not in Grozny in Chechnya, in all of Chechnya,
га не не в Грозном в Чечне во всей Чечне
that is, in Chechnya, more children died
да то есть в Чечне погибло детей больше
than in gas so
чем в газе так
Well,
Ну
dadada, if you take gas on October 7th of this
дадада если газ взять 7 октября сего
day, then there are 17,000 already on Dan. I
числа то там 17000 уже на Дан я
understand correctly that you just Chechens
правильно понимаю что вы просто чеченцы
closed your eyes, I’ll take a sip of it Yes, and you forgave the
закрыли глаза глотну это Да и простили
Russians for the murder of your 4,000 children, 300,000
русским убийство ваших 4000 детей 300000
of yours, you want more Yes, they died,
ваших ты хочешь чтобы ещё Да погибло
no, I’m just  I asked, this is
нене я ж просто спросил чу это
the sixth
шесто
That is, I correctly understand that you
То есть я правильно понимаю что вы
submitted, surrendered like Russia,
покорились сдались типа России
yes Hey I Well, well, I don’t know, in short, it
да Эй я Ну так Ну не знаю короче так
turned out Well, it turns out Well, it
получилось Ну так получается Ну
turns out like this, that is, you in order
получается так то есть вы для того чтобы
not to want to continue Yes, you gave up and
не захотели дальше Да вы сдались и
said, closed your eyes, pretended  We all
сказали закрыли глаза сделали вид Всё мы
won’t remember about the murdered 40,000 of
не будем вспоминать про убитых 40.000
our little
наших маленьких
Chechens. Well, what can we do? War is
чеченцев Ну это что поделать война
like that, people unfortunately, civilians
такова люди к сожалению мирные жители
die too. And at that time, every
тоже погибают А в то время каждый мирный
civilian fought, every civilian fought, a child who
человек воевал каждый Мирный воевал
died fought, 40,000
ребёнок который погиб воевал 40.000
children died. Yes, yes, yes there were yes Children too.
детей погиб Да да да были да Дети тоже
who fought 40,000 children died,
были которые воевал 40.000 детей погибло
here are 40,000 children who fought, well, you yourself Well,
вот 40.000 детей воевало ну ты сам са Ну
newborns, newborns don’t
новорождённые новорождённые их не
count them until they’re 76 years old, they also don’t count were with don’t count don’t
считают до 76 лет также не считают были
count who don’t don’t count
счита не считают которые не не считают
who fought Well, they won’t fight in any way
которые воевали Ну они же никак не будут
because everything is so Well
воевать потому что воз такой Ну к
Unfortunately, it turned out that way, but there were children
сожалению так получилось но были дети
who, uh, fought. Well, there
которые ээ воевали Ну сколько таких
were a lot of them, very few of them, because there
было очень много очень мало потому что
weren’t that many weapons, so that even the
оружия столько не было да Чтобы ещё и то
children could carry all the weapons. Yes,
детё чтобы таскало всё ну оружие Да у
we only had machine guns, and it
нас у нас автоматы были только так и
turns out that look now, that’s
получается что смотри теперь да
all  Russian Chechens consider themselves
все чеченцы русские считают себя
winners Yes, the Russians bent you over, they
победителями Да русские нагнули вас они
raped your mothers and grandparents
насиловали ваших матерей бабушек дедушек
Yes, they killed your babies And now you
Да убивали ваших младенцев А теперь вы
look them calmly in the eyes and
им смотрите спокойно в глаза и
smile
улыбаетесь
Well, you understand, the
Ну понимаешь
Russians are the kind of nation that needs to be
русские это такая нация которую нужно
respected, this is the
уважать это нация
kind of nation so as not to fight with it, in order to be
такая чтобы не воевать с ней чтобы быть
with  her and be friends with her That is,
с ней и дружить с ней То есть
you are definitely a Highlander You are definitely from the
ты Ты точно Горец Ты точно с
Caucasus Well, yes, we Highlanders should How would we
Кавказа Ну да мы Горцы должны Как бы
respect every nationality? I’m
уважать каждую национальность мне мне
interested, that is, when your ancestors would
интересно то есть когда ваши бы предки
say, you know, even since the time of Yermolov, when
сказали знаете ещ со врем Ермолова когда
Russian troops in the Caucasus killed everyone there
российские войска на Кавказ убивали там
and  and there I think this one comes to the Imam
и и там думаю приходит такой на Имам
Shamil and says, you know, we must You
шамиле говорит знаете мы должны Ты
know Imam Shamil Yes, I know Imam Shamil
знаешь Имама Шамиля Да знаю Имама Шамиля
Yes, and the story about the Guni and I know everything, yes And
Да и историю про гуни и всё знаю да И
how he ended, I also know
чем закончил он тоже знаю Так
So And what
что И что
happens Russia came with a lot of
получается Россия прила количеством
people with great
людей большими
technologies killed people Yes
технологиями поубивал людей Да по
I slaughtered entire villages back
вырезала целые сёла ещё
then, but they didn’t give me a reason to
тогда а повод же они не давали чтобы так
do this. Who are
делать Кто
they, well, Russians? I mean, they came to
они ну русские В смысле по они пришли на
your land, they slaughtered your people, they
вашу землю вырезали ваших людей
captured
захватили
everything, well, it happens, it
всё ну бывает сказать бывает понял
happens;  the war
вот я понимаю там вы проиграли эту войну
and silently would sit there, you know, look
и молча там бы ну сидели знаешь смотрели
scythe at the Russians And so you say
коса на русских А так вы рассказываете
we are Putin’s loyal dogs there, that’s how this
мы верные там собаки Путина вот как этот
Kadyrov says there We
Кадыров говорит там Мы там всё мы
will do everything there Vladimir Vladimirovich there, in short,
сделаем Владимир Владимирович там короче
he’s almost licking his ass here’s a
аж прям чуть ли не задницу ему
cut for you by Jakhar Dudayev
лижит вот для тебя джахар Дудаев крой
or a
или
traitor is a murderer for you, Jakhar Dudayev
предатель убийца для тебя джахар Дудаев
is a murderer Well, it’s like because of him it
убийца Ну да он как бы из-за него это
all started, you understand it
всё началось всё понимаешь
yourself Why because of
сам Почему из-за
him because of him 300,000 Why from him
него из-за него 300.000 Почему из него
look Chechnya, your people declared
смотри Чечня ваш народ провозгласил
independence in the nineties, and even
независимость в девяностом году да ещё
when from the Soviet  Unions of different
когда из Советского Союза разные
Republics Yes He came he was elected
Республики Да Приходили он его избрали
president of Ichkeria Chechen Republic of
президентом Ичкерии Чеченской республики
Ichkeria he came he could have stayed
Ичкерии он приехал он мог быть остаться
in Russia and he could have received a pension there
в России да мог быть там себе пенсию
Yes he came to the Soviet Union to
получать Да советскую он приехал чтобы
be with his people yes he yes it is worthy
быть со своим народом да он да достойно
that he wanted to be his people but not  it’s
то что он хотел быть своим народом но не
worthy how he did it all
достойно то как он это всё сделал так
so he didn’t do it attacked aln
что сделал не он напал альн
attacked what And what is the reason What is the
напал какой А в чём повод Какой
reason Well freedom independence of your
повод Ну свободу независимость своей
country So it’s not him it’s the Chechen people
страны Так это не он это чеченский народ
look uh
смотри
independence was proclaimed by the
ээ независимость была провозглашена
Congress of the Chechen people look
конгрессом чеченского народа смотри
open Wikipedia If you don’t know the
открываешь Википедию Если ты не знаешь
history  of his country Yes, what’s
историю своей страны Да а что там
written there is good, I’m interested, it’s
написано хорошо мне интересно
just ninety, and so on June 8,
просто вот девяностом так вот 8 июня
ninety-one, the proclamation by the
девяносто первого года провозглашение
national congress of the Chechen
общенациональным конгрессом чеченского
people of the Chechen Republic nokh chich That is, it was
народа Чеченской республики нох чичь Вот
not he who proclaimed it
то есть это не он провозгласил это
Elders, I don’t know what you
Старейшин вот я не знаю как у вас этот
call this in your opinion  organ Yes, when the
называется по-вашему орган Да когда
elders of these different ones are called Tatars
старейшины разных этих вот татара та
Yes, he just
Да он просто он
undertook to be president Yes, he
взялся быть президентом Да он
undertook
взялся
these state
эти государственные
institutions and he When the first
институты и он Когда началась первая
Chechen war began In the ninety-something
чеченская В девяносто чем
year, look, in the ninety-ninety-
году то смотри в девяностом и девяносто
first year they declared independence, and until the
первом провозгласили независимость да до
ninety-something year Chechnya was
девяносто чего года Чечня была
independent  Russia brought in troops,
независимой войска Россия ввела в
but few countries recognized it at that time,
де но мало стран признало это в то время
only Georgia recognized Russia
только одна Грузия признавала Россия
recognized that it was part of it. So it
признавала что она в составе Так что это
doesn’t matter at all, you understand.
не имеет никакого значения понимаешь са
Well, Russia, look, Russia came to kill
Ну Россия смотри Россия пришла убивать
these people, and then after the first
людей этих да потом после первой
Chechen war they were in Khasavyurt. This is after  the
чеченской были же Хасавюрте Это после
first Chechen Well, yes, Russia
первой чеченской Ну да да Россия
agreed to withdraw troops and further
согласилось вывести войска и дальше
discuss the issue of independence of the
обсуждать вопрос о независимости
Chechen Republic of Ichkeria, what did
Чеченской республики Ичкерии что сделала
Russia do? Licking the wounds and attacking, made the
Россия Подлиза раны и напала сделала
second Chechen
вторую чеченскую
You deceived
Ты что обмануло
you, but
вас а
well, the attack on Dagestan
хорошо нападение на Дагестан тебе ни о
doesn’t tell you anything again, again, this is
чём не говорит ещё раз ещё раз это по
why  there are no reasons, yes, that is,
вот там поводы не поводы да то есть
Russia is doing everything to accumulate strength and
Россия делает всё чтобы накопить силы и
attack just like with us, like yes, it
напасть так же как с нами типа да
turns out they attacked. Then come on, let’s go with the Minsk agreements. Yes, it has accumulated accumulated
минские соглашения Да накопила накопила
strength, it attacked even more, it’s trying to capture
силы напала ещё больше пробует захватить
absolutely the same thing. And with you, that’s
абсолютно тоже самое И с вами вот и
all and the most important thing  Yes,
всё и самое основное Да
you perceive them as Russians there, I won’t
вы русскими воспринимаете там не буду
even say what words they
говорить даже Какими словами Они Вас
call you, these nasty ones, but for them
называют этими противными да для них
you and for them you are there is something, so they
Вы да для них вы там что-то вот они
want you to be in Russia, but so that you
хотят чтобы вы были в России но чтобы вы
don’t come to Moscow, that’s when Chechnya
не приезжали в Москву вот когда Чечня
should be included  Russian
должна быть в составе Российской
Federation Chechens Citizens of the Russian
Федерации чеченцы Граждане Российской
Federation but for some reason the Chechens of Red
Федерации но почему-то чеченцы Красной
Square they don’t want to be
площади они не хотят уже
on Red Square Desh on but on
на на Красной площади Деш на но на
Red Square these are already some
Красной площади это уже какие-то
unpleasant Chechens, but let them
неприятные чеченцы да вот пусть они
sit somewhere in Chechnya and not come out
где-то сидят у себя в Чечне и не вылазят
yes  that is, let them only give
да то есть Пусть дают только
us resources and soldiers, that’s all,
нам ресурсы и солдат вот и всё к
unfortunately, yes. Well, it
сожалению да Ну всё же поделать Ну
can be done. Well, it turned out that way. You were also part of the same,
получилось Вы же тоже были в соста ипе
we were part of the Russian Empire, and
были мы в составе Российской империи и
we were part of the Soviet Union and
мы были в составе Советского Союза и
strived for Independence and
стремились к Независимости и
were liberated, yes.  And when we were
освободились да И когда мы были в
part of the Soviet Union Yes, there were also
составе Советского Союза Да тоже были
people like you, for example, who
люди такие как ты например которые там
licked asses in Moscow, they are there,
лизали задницы в Москве они там вот
Moscow, we should be with Moscow and so
Москва мы должны быть с Москвой и так
on, Despite the fact that Moscow killed
дальше Несмотря на то что Москва убивала
our ancestors and there were people who
наших предков а были люди которые
said that there should be  independence
говорили что должна быть независимость
Okay And the fact that you bombed your Donetsk,
Окей А то что вы бомбили своих Донец
which is normal? This is a fairy tale that they
что нормально Это это сказка которую
tell you to
тебе рассказывают для того чтобы
justify the attack on Ukraine Look
оправдать нападение на Украину Посмотри
if we bombed Donetsk Lugansk Look
если мы бомбили Донецк Луганск Посмотри
if we bombed Donetsk Lugansk for 8 years
если мы 8 лет бомбили Донецк Луганск
look at the photos Why Donetsk and
посмотри фотографии Почему Донецк и
Lugansk stand and everything works and everything  it’s
Луганск стоит и весь работает да всё
standing and Mariupol, which seems to have been liberated, has been
стоит а Мариуполь который как освободили
destroyed And Bakhmut, which seems to have
уничтожен А бахмут который вроде как
been liberated, has been destroyed, the solidar, which
освобождают уничтожен солидар который
has been liberated, seems to have been destroyed Why where is
освободили вроде уничтожен Почему там
Ukraine Bombed for 8 years, everything is standing
где Украина Бомбила 8 лет всё стоит
trolleybuses run in Donetsk Yes,
троллейбусы ходят в Донецке Да
universities work, people live Yes, and
университеты работают люди живут Да а
where Russia liberated everything is an ass
там где Россия освободила там всё [__]
Don’t you think that  you are
Тебе не кажется что тебя
being deceived, I don’t know for sure that now they are
обманывают не я точно знаю что сейчас
sending people from here to build a
отсюда отправляют людей чтобы построить
building that was destroyed by your
здание которое были разрушены от ваших
shelling, our shelling,
вот обстрелов наших обстрелов
look
смотри
maul, you destroyed Mariupol, so the buildings there are poison and the people who
мауль вы уничтожили Мариуполь так здани
build the people there are
там отрава а людей кто строит людей
no people in Mariupol there was half a million
нету в Мариуполе было полмиллиона
population, where
населения куда оно
did it go, they probably moved
делось переселились наверно а погибших
how many died? Whom Whom to rebuild there
сколько Кого Кого там отстраивать
[music]
[музыка]
just for the picture for the families who
просто для картинки для семеи которые
will live there Who will live there
будут там жить Кто будет там жить там
either died or
либо умерли либо
left Well, those who left will return
уехали Ну те которые уехали вернутся
Where
Куда
Why to
Зачем в
Mariupol, here in Ukraine a lot of people
Мариуполь вот у нас в Украине куча людей
left Mariupol where they will not return
уехали из Мариуполя куда они не вернутся
there Even those who went to Russia, they wo
туда Даже те кто в Россию уехал они туда
n’t return there
не вернутся
Why Yes, I do
Зачем
n’t know, in
Да не знаю
short,
короче
nenya where you spoke from Kiev and the
неня там где ты ты говорил из Киева да
mills where Khmelnitsky
мельниц где Хмельницке
khmelnitsy everything is
хмельниц всё вот
like this, the
так манкуртом
Empire is producing mankurt, subscribe to my Telegram
плодит Империя подпишись на мий Telegram
right now ovin and
прям зараз овин а
pok tse more and more respectfully YouTube  occupying
пок це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube заня
us through the skarg ORV your ban and a
нас через скарг ОРВ твый бан и дуже
lot of video I don’t show people often I don’t
багато видео не показую людям вчасно не
show information about streams for that in order
показуе информация про стримы тому для
for Mali to write an operational link
того щоб ми Мали оперативный звязок
right away and Popik there in
пишиться прямо зараз а Попик там в
Telegra okrim video sche tezh Tsikava and
телегра окрим видео ще теж цикава и
Korisna information and we’ll blame you on
корисна информация и мы повинни з вами
Trima  postiyny operational link is
трима постийний оперативный звязок
independent in that chi
незалежно в того
show you about it YouTube Glory to
чи покаже вам про це YouTube Слава
Ukraine
Украине
write
пиши